// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1) ________ apple?",
    answer: "An",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "Many"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2)_______ Mango.",
    answer: "A",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "3)______ Pen.",
    answer: "A",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "Two",
      "The"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "4)________ boys.",
    answer: "The",
    options: ["A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "5)________ anchor.",
    answer: "An",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6)_________ umbrella.",
    answer: "An",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "7)________ sun.",
    answer: "The",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "8)________ ear",
    answer: "An",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "9)________ Owl.",
    answer: "An",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "10)_________ Himalayas",
    answer: "The",
    options: [
      "A",
      "An",
       "The",
      "None"
    ]
  },
];